JAN MICHAEL CAASI

JUNIOR WEB DEVELOPER



+639997543046



janmichaelcaasi@gmail.com



San Mateo, Rizal



https://www.linkedin.com/in/jancaasi-53ab30277/

LINKS

Portfolio: https://portfolio-v2-

xcmy.onrender.com

Github: https://github.com/jantoy052003

SKILLS

- Front-End
 - HTML, CSS, JavaScript, ReactJS, Tailwind, Bootstrap
- Back-End
 - PHP. Laravel
- Database
 - MvSQL
- Collaboration Tools
 - o Github, Teams, Zoom, MS Office, Canva
- Team player and a leader
- Critical thinker
- Able to multi-task
- · Results-oriented

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF ARTS IN COMMUNICATION

University of the Philippines Baguio 2003-2006

PROFILE

To carry through the goals of a web developer and to be globally competitive to further strengthen my skills and knowledge as a Full-stack Web Developer by working with great sense of responsibility, dedication and hard work, such that, whatever expertise, training or skills I gain will be used for development and share in the further growth of the company.

EXPERIENCE

KODEGO BOOTCAMP GRADUATE

KodeGo

February - May 2023

- Focused on full-stack web development
- Built three outstanding website projects as part of training requirement two are with a team
- Provided back-end codes that won our team the best capstone project within the class:

https://mindfull-tasks-app.onrender.com/

TIER 2 TECHNICAL SUPPORT ADVISOR

TDCX Philippines

2020-2022

- Served as a Tier 2 technical support advisor for Apple
- Handled Tier 1 escalation cases and consults.
- Hand picked by management to be part of mentoring team who assisted and taught new employees and Tier 2 advisors.

MANAGEMENT TRAINEE/ STALL SUPERVISOR

Wooleejeep Pte. Ltd (Singapore)

2012-2015

- Trained new staff and made sure new staff adheres to the company's quality standards
- Responsible for daily operations from opening to closing of outlet
- Ensure cleanliness of equipment and food hygiene is followed by all staff